MOHAMMED ALI HACHICHA

Developer

+216 24 077 446

@ dalyhachicha7@gmail.com

daly-hachicha.webflow.io

Tunisia, Sfax

SUMMARY

Having a passion for computers has led me to expand my knowledge in computer science from a young age. I was absolutely attracted to computer software and games which later developed into an interest in programming.

I am mostly self-taught, as well as having a fundamental license degree in computer science from the Higher Institute of Computer Science of Mahdia.

I also have some experience developing mobile and web applications as a freelancer.

SKILLS

Computer Vision

Machine Lerning & Al

Flask/Django

Mobile Dev (Flutter)

MongoDB

Firebase

SQL

Data Structure and Algorithms

API's

GitHub

EXPERIENCE

Python Developer

🛗 2018 - Ongoing

Freelance

- Modified existing software to correct coding errors, upgrade and improve overall performance.
- Implimented simple machine learning algorithms (Linear Regression, Decision tree, Random forest).
- Implimented inceptionV3 model for face shape classification (end of studies project).
- Implimented OpenCV and mediapipe for extracting face landmarks (end of studies project).

Flutter Developer

🛗 2021 - Ongoing

Freelance

- Modified existing projects to correct coding errors, upgrade and improve overall performance
- Implementation of Firebase
- Design and developed 2 apps
- Integration/Widget/Unit Testing

PROGRAMMING

Python Proficient	••••
Dart Advanced	••••
HTML/CSS/JS Advanced	••••
SQL Intermediate	••••
C/PHP/VB.NET Rusty	• • • •

EDUCATION

Bachelor degree in Computer Science

Hedi SOUSSI high school - Sfax

iii july 2018

Fundamental License in Computer Science

Higher Institue of Computer Science

- Mahdia (ISIMA)

10/2018 - 07/2021

STRENGTHS



